TZE FUNG JIM LUNG

1067, 59th Street, Brooklyn, NY 11219

Tel: (917) 214 – 0908 | fung10_91@hotmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/tze-fung-lung-0a9111164/

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Bilingual master graduate in data science with data analysis experience seeking a challenging position in the data analysis and engineering field where relevant expertise can be utilized

SKILLS

Excellent working knowledge of R and Python for financial analysis and Data Science skills. Other areas of expertise include data scraping, data cleaning and imputation, data visualization, data mining and modeling, machine learning, Hadoop, Mathematics and statistics programming. BI analysis tool – Mode and Google data Studio. Foreign language: Cantonese and Mandarin

Work Sample: https://fung1091.shinyapps.io/profile/

EDUCATION

Master's Degree of Data Science at City University of New York (CUNY) (April 2019, GPA: 3.9)

BEng in Manufacturing Informatics and Systems Engineering from City University of Hong Kong

Bachelor of Health Science from RMIT University

EXPERIENCE

Sales Operation Specialist – Center Plan Healthy Living (CPHL)

Dec. 2020 - Now

- Conducted Data Reporting analysis to generate daily, weekly and monthly visualization report
- Analyzed internal and external data (CMS gov)
- Work Sample: https://datastudio.google.com/reporting/8d0d6cd6-298e-46c3-b162-6897f2f07be3

Freelance Data Analyst – Various clients

May. 2019 – Nov.2020

 Provided complex and intensive data analysis related to data scraping, visualization, mining, and Excel formation and Pivot table

Intern - Kasisto, New York, NY

Jan. 2019 – Apr. 2019

- Improved and extracted the data sourcing pipeline and the natural language in chat-bot
- Developed and supported of a wide range of data transformations and migrations
- Constructed custom ETL processes

Co-Founder - Newinsock.com, New York, NY

Jan. 2017 – Dec. 2018

Conducted sourcing for products to ensure constant and timely supply of inventory; coordinated shipping and professional
packaging for product orders; provided detailed follow-through and after sales service for customer satisfaction

Safety Officer – PCCW Solutions, Hong Kong

Dec. 2015 - Dec. 2016

- Organized details and workflow of a safety and health training program
- Performed daily inspection for various parts of the project and recorded all documentations and procedures involved
- Prepared detailed training records, inspection reports, inspection photos, drill reports and accident records

QUALIFICATIONS AND CREDENTIALS

Real Estate License (Jan. 2018); Graduate Member – Institution of Occupational Safety and Health (2014)